



Kalmargade 28, Aarhus N



+ 45 27 60 51 70



gabor.jezerniczky@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/gaborjezerniczky/



mrjezy.github.ic



CORE COMPETENCIES

Communication

Data management

Machine Learning

Problem solving

Statistics

Reporting

**



TECHNICAL SKILLS

R

Excel / VBA

SQL

Python

**



LANGUAGES

Hungarian

English

Danish

**

German

 $\star\star$

Gábor Jezerniczky

I am an enthusiastic data analyst with 5 years of work experience in different roles and areas of multinational businesses. My main objective is to find a role in a company, where I can identify the underlying meaning of structured and unstructured data and provide business value from it. My curiosity and global perspective always help me to find an optimal solution for a given problem.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist Trainee

Vestas Wind Systems, Aarhus, Denmark April 2017 –

Responsible for developing machine learning algorithms for various data science driven projects, such as outlier detection in material master data or categorical data classification using R, SQL and Microsoft Visual Studio.

Student Worker

Vestas Wind Systems, Aarhus, Denmark June 2016 – June 2017

Responsible for developing and maintaining Project Management templates in Excel and VBA, creating reports with SQL.

Purchaser

Duna-Dráva Cement Kft., Vác, Hungary July 2010 – October 2013

Responsible for purchasing energy (electricity, natural gas) and various materials for the market leading hungarian cement plant. I revised and cleaned up the master data for these material categories in SAP R/3 MM.



EDUCATION

MSc in Business Intelligence

Aarhus University, Aarhus, Denmark September 2015 – June 2017

Master thesis title: A search and classification engine for cleantech data

BA in Economics and Business Administration

Heller Farkas College of Economics and Tourism, Budapest, Hungary

September 2005 – July 2009

Specialization: Logistics